[Music]
Hi everyone. In this video, we'll
explore how to access and use a reports
feature in Blitzet to track your
productivity and get insights on how you
spend your work time. First, let's see
how to access reports. From the home
screen, simply tap the reports icon in
the bottom navigation bar. This opens
your reports dashboard where all your
productivity data is displayed. At the
top of the reports page, you'll find
filters to customize your view. You can
filter by specific lists to focus on
particular projects or areas of work or
select all lists to see your overall
stats. You can also select date range to
analyze your productivity over time
using quick shortcuts or a custom range.
Below the filters, you'll see a graph
and key stats that summarize your
activity. These stats reflect data
collected from when you rent tasks live
or took breaks. Total work days. It
shows the number of days you actively
worked in Blitzer during the selected
period.
Total tasks done. This one shows how
many tasks you completed during this
period. Plus the average number of tasks
completed per workday, meaning the days
you actually worked in Blitz. Total
hours worked. It is a total time spent
on tasks and breaks along with your
average daily hours worked.
Average time per task. This one tells
you how long you typically spend on each
task, including both completed tasks and
those started but not finished yet. The
graph breaks down your daily sessions
into task time, break time, and total
session time, giving you a clear visual
presentation of how each day is spent.
You can click on this metrics here to
toggle them on or off and select the
data you want to see. Next, let's scroll
down to see the most productive times.
The most productive hour shows when
you're most focused during the day.
Blitz tracks when you go live as tasks
and identifies a pick active hour within
the selected date range. The most
productive day highlights a week day
with the most sessions run. The most
productive month shows the month you
were most active. If your selected range
covers multiple month range covers only
one month, that month will be displayed
here. Here goes the time by list
section. It breaks down your total work
time by each list. So you can see where
you are investing the most effort and
how much time you spent per list.
Finally, we have the done tasks section.
Here the list shows all your completed
tasks with timestamps showing the exact
day you finished them. It also tells you
if you completed tasks early or late.
This data is available only if you set
an AS for the task. On the right, you'll
see how much time you spent on each task
based on the tasks time taken field. The
punctuality graph shows what percentage
of your task time was finished early
versus late. For example, if you spend
15 hours finishing tasks early and 5
hours finishing them late, the graph
will display the ratio as 75% early and
25% late. So, that's how Blit Reports
work. Use this insights to better
understand your work patterns, improve
your planning, and boost your
productivity. If you found this video
helpful, be sure to check out our other
tutorials and join our Discord community
for more tips and support. Happy
blitzing.
[Music]